{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"260/10",
			"answer":"260/10",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"192/16",
			"answer":"192/16",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"630/63",
			"answer":"630/63",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"352/32",
			"answer":"352/32",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"360/15",
			"answer":"360/15",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"420/60",
			"answer":"420/60",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"136/68",
			"answer":"136/68",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"459/27",
			"answer":"459/27",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"747/83",
			"answer":"747/83",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"388/97",
			"answer":"388/97",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}
	]
}